Storrs Agricultural Experiment Station Records 1972.0001
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Library
- Series I: Correspondence, 1897-1920
  - Farmers Trust Company, 1906; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box4:42 (Box-folder 4:42, Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Farmers Voice and National Rural, 1903; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box4:43 (Box 4, Folder 43, Box-folder 4:43)
  - Fay, John H., 1907-1918; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box4:44 (Box-folder 4:44, Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Fay, John N., 1909-1910; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box4:45 (Box-folder 4:45, Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Fe - Fin, 1905-1919; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box4:46 (Box-folder 4:46, Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Felber, John J., 1908-1912; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box4:47 (Box-folder 4:47, Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Felt and Tarrant Manufacturng Company, 1898-1912; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box4:48 (Box-folder 4:48, Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Fenn, Fred, 1909-1910; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box4:49 (Box-folder 4:49, Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Ferguson, Allen, 1907; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box4:50 (Box-folder 4:50, Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Field Force Pump Co., 1908-1910; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box4:51 (Box-folder 4:51, Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Fienemann, C.F., 1908-1909; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box4:52 (Box 4, Folder 52, Box-folder 4:52)
  - Fip - For, 1911-1920; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box4:53 (Box 4, Folder 53, Box-folder 4:53)
  - Fisher, O.D., 1907; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box4:54 (Box-folder 4:54, Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Fisk Teachers Agencies, 1908-1909; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box4:55 (Box 4, Folder 55, Box-folder 4:55)
  - Folmer and Schwing Division Easman Kodak Co., 1911-1913; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box4:56 (Box-folder 4:56, Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Forbush, Erwin H., 1908-1911; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box4:57 (Box 4, Folder 57, Box-folder 4:57)
  - Fos - Fraz, 1898-1920; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box4:58 (Box-folder 4:58, Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Foss, G. Herbert, 1920; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box4:59 (Box 4, Folder 59, Box-folder 4:59)
  - Foster, A. L., 1905-1907; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box4:60 (Box 4, Folder 60)
    Correspondence; Storrs (inhabited place); Connecticut (state); Storrs Agricultural Experiment Station
  - Foster, Walter N., 1906-1912; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box4:61 (Box 4, Folder 61, Box-folder 4:61)
  - Fottler, Fishe, Rawson Co., 1910-1911; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box4:62 (Box-folder 4:62, Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Fouts, L. M., 1903; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box4:63 (Box 4, Folder 63, Box-folder 4:63)
  - Fowler, W. W., 1903; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box4:64 (Box-folder 4:64)
    Storrs (inhabited place); Connecticut (state); Correspondence; Storrs Agricultural Experiment Station
  - Fox, J. M., 1910-1911; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box4:65 (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - France, 1900-1916; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box4:66 (Box-folder 4:66)
    Storrs (inhabited place); Connecticut (state); Correspondence; France (nation); Storrs Agricultural Experiment Station
  - Fre - Fun, 1911-1920; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box4:67 (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - Frisbie, M. M., 1902-1911; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box4:68 (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - Frost, Willis E., 1908-1919; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box4:69 (Box-folder 4:69)
  - Fuller, Edward A., 1909; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box4:70 (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - Funk Brothers Seed Company, undated; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box4:71 (Box-folder 4:71)
  - G - Gas, 1907-1920; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box4:72 (Box 4, Folder 72, Box-folder 4:72)
  - Gallup, Earl N., 1909-1912; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box4:73 (Box-folder 4:73)
  - Gamble, J. A., 1907-1912; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box4:74 (Box 4, Folder 74)
  - Garrigus, Harry L., 1907-1920; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box4:75 (Box-folder 4:75)
  - Garton Seed Company, 1908-1914; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box4:76 (Box-folder 4:76)
  - Gat - Gill, 1910-1915; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box4:77 (Box-folder 4:77)
  - General Electric Co., 1907; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box4:77a (Box-folder 4:77a, Box 4, Folder 77a)
  - George Batten Company, 1908; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box4:78 (Box 4, Folder 78)
  - George L. Harding, 1905; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box4:79 (Box-folder 4:79)
  - George Murphy Inc., 1907; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box4:80 (Box 4, Folder 80, Box-folder 4:80)
  - George, Gilbert, 1909; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box4:81 (Box-folder 4:81)
  - Georgia Experiment Station, 1912-1914; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box4:82 (Box 4, Folder 82)
  - German Kali Works, 1903-1914; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box4:83 (Box-folder 4:83)
  - Germany, 1888-1914; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box4:84 (Box-folder 4:84)
    Storrs (inhabited place); Connecticut (state); Correspondence; Germany (nation); Storrs Agricultural Experiment Station
  - Gibson, Howard B., undated; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box4:85 (Box 4, Folder 85)
  - Gilford, John E. Coopert, 1918; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box4:86 (Box-folder 4:86)
  - Gilbert and Barber Manufacturing Company, 1912-1914; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box4:87 (Box 4, Folder 87)
  - Gille - Gl, 1903-1917; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box4:88 (Box-folder 4:88)
  - Gillette, Herbert A., 1910-1912; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box4:89 (Box 4, Folder 89)
  - Ginn and Company, 1909-1912; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box4:90 (Box-folder 4:90)
  - Go - Gow, 1906-1920; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box4:91 (Box 4, Folder 91)
  - Gold, T. S., 1888-1892; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box4:92 (Box 4, Folder 92)
  - Gold, T. S., 1893-1894; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box4:93 (Box-folder 4:93)
  - Gold, T. S., 1895; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box4:94 (Box 4, Folder 94)
  - Gold, T. S., 1896; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box4:95 (Box-folder 4:95)
  - Gold, T. S., 1897; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box4:96 (Box 4, Folder 96)
  - Gold, T. S., 1898; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box4:97 (Box-folder 4:97)
  - Gold, T. S., 1899; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box4:98 (Box 4, Folder 98)
  - Gold, T. S. and Atwater, Wilbur O., 1900; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box4:99; Atwater, W. O. (Wilbur Olin), 1844-1907 (Box-folder 4:99)
  - Gould, Ralph E., 1904-1908; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box4:100 (Box 4, Folder 100)
  - Goulds Manufacturing Company, 1903-1911; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box4:101 (Box-folder 4:101)
  - Gr - Griff, 1911-1919; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box4:102 (Box 4, Folder 102)
  - Graham, C. K., 1905-1907; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box4:103 (Box-folder 4:103)
  - Grant, Edwin M., 1908; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box4:104 (Box 4, Folder 104)
  - G. R. Burdick, 1898; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box5:1 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Grasselle Chemical Company, 1902-1917; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box5:2 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Graves, Charles B., 1910-1912; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box5:3 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Gray, F. W., 1907-1911; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box5:4 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Great Britain, 1898-1915; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box5:5 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Greenfield Country Club Agricultural Fair, 1906-1908; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box5:6 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Greims, Herbert Spencer, 1910; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box5:7 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Griffin, M. E., 1908-1910; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box5:8 (Box-folder 5:8)
  - Griffith and Turner Company, 1907-1908; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box5:9 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Grig - Guy, 1910-1920; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box5:10 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Grisbrook, E. D., 1910-1912; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box5:11 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Grover, J. Stillwell, 1908; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box5:12 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Guernsey Cattle Club, 1904; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box5:13 (Box-folder 5:13)
  - Gulley, A. G., 1913-1914; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box5:14 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - H (Business), 1904-1907; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box5:15 (Box-folder 5:15, Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Hood - Hyde, 1904; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box5:16 (Box-folder 5:16)
  - H, 1908; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box5:17 (Box-folder 5:17, Box 5, Folder 17)
  - H, 1908; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box5:18 (Box 5, Folder 18, Box-folder 5:18)
  - H - I (Business), 1908; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box5:19 (Box-folder 5:19)
  - H, 1909; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box5:20 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - H, 1909; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box5:21 (Box-folder 5:21)
  - H - L (Business), 1909; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box5:22 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - H, 1910; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box5:23 (Box-folder 5:23)
  - H (Business), 1918; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box5:24 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - H (Business), 1917; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box5:25 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - H, 1917; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box5:26 (Box-folder 5:26)
  - H, 1916; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box5:27 (Box-folder 5:27)
  - H - I, 1915; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box5:28 (Box-folder 5:28)
  - H - J (Business), 1915; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box5:29 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - H, 1914; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box5:30 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - H, 1914; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box5:31 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - H, 1914; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box5:32 (Box-folder 5:32)
  - H - J (Business), 1913; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box5:33 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - H, 1913; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box5:34 (Box-folder 5:34)
  - H (Business), 1912 March 5; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box5:35 (Box-folder 5:35)
  - H, 1912; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box5:36 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - H - I (Business), 1911; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box5:36 (Box 5, Folder 36a)
  - H, 1911; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box5:37 (Box-folder 5:37, Box 5, Folder 37)
  - H, 1911; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box5:38 (Box 5, Folder 38, Box-folder 5:38)
  - H - I (Business), 1910; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box5:39 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - H, 1910; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box5:40 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - H, 1910; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box5:41 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - H, 1918; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box5:42 (Box-folder 5:42)
  - H, 1919; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box5:43 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - H - I (Business), 1919; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box5:44 (Box-folder 5:44)
  - H, 1920; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box5:45 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - H (Business), 1920; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box5:46 (Box-folder 5:46)
  - H.C. Haywood and Co. (Blickensderfer Typewriter), 1898; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box5:47 (Box 5, Folder 47)
    Correspondence; Storrs (inhabited place); Connecticut (state); Typewriters; Storrs Agricultural Experiment Station; Blickensderfer Manufacturing Company.
  - H.C. Judd and Root, 1902-1903; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box5:48 (Box-folder 5:48)
  - H - O Company, 1907; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box5:49 (Box-folder 5:49)
  - Hale, J.H. (Hale's Fruits), 1907; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box5:50 (Box-folder 5:50)
  - Hall, William H., 1902; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box5:51 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Hamm, Montague, 1905; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box5:52 (Box-folder 5:52)
  - Hammond, C. D., 1895; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box5:53 (Box-folder 5:53)
  - Hampshire Paper Company, 1902; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box5:54 (Box-folder 5:54)
  - Harmony Grange, 1908; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box5:55 (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Harvard University, 1907; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box5:56 (Box-folder 5:56)
  - Harvey and Lewis, 1905; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box5:57 (Box-folder 5:57)
  - Hawaii, 1908; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box5:58 (Box 5, Folder 58)
    Correspondence; Storrs (inhabited place); Connecticut (state); Hawaii (state); Storrs Agricultural Experiment Station
  - Hawley, Jospeh R., 1898; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box5:59 (Box-folder 5:59, Box 5, Folder 59)
    Storrs (inhabited place); Connecticut (state); Agricultural experiment stations; Storrs Agricultural Experiment Station
  - Healey, L. H., 1888-1905; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box5:60 (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - Henry Field Seed Company, 1909-1914; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box5:61 (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - Henry, E. Stevens, 1900-1902; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box5:62 (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - Henshaw, John, 1904; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box5:63 (Box-folder 5:63)
  - Herbert T. Clarke, 1907-1908; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box5:64 (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - Herring - Hall - Marvin Safe Co., 1902; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box5:65 (Box-folder 5:65)
  - Hickox, William B., 1903; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box5:66 (Box 5, Folder 66, Box-folder 5:66)
  - Hill, Ebenezer, 1904; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box5:67 (Box-folder 5:67, Box 5, Folder 67)
  - Holland, 1899-1914; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box5:68 (Box 5, Folder 68, Box-folder 5:68)
    Netherlands; Storrs (inhabited place); Connecticut (state); Correspondence; Storrs Agricultural Experiment Station
  - Holman, William, 1902; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box5:69 (Box 5, Folder 69)
  - Holman (William D.), Treasurer, Storrs Agricultural Experiment Station, 1900; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box5:70 (Box-folder 5:70)
    Correspondence; Storrs (inhabited place); Connecticut (state); Storrs Agricultural Experiment Station; Holman, William D., Treasurer, Storrs Agricultural Experiment Station
  - Holman, William D., Treasurer, Storrs Agricultural Experiment Station, 1901; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box5:71 (Box-folder 5:71)
  - Home Correspondence School, 1904-1905; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box5:72 (Box-folder 5:72)
  - Hood, C. I., 1906; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box5:73 (Box-folder 5:73)
  - Hoopes and Townsend, 1898; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box5:74 (Box-folder 5:74)
  - Hoosier Drill Company, 1905-1906; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box5:75 (Box-folder 5:75)
  - Hopson, George A., 1901-1902; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box5:76 (Box-folder 5:76)
  - Hopson G. A., 1901; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box5:77 (Box 5, Folder 77)
  - Houghton, F. L., 1905; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box5:78 (Box-folder 5:78)
  - Howitt, J. E., 1906; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box5:79 (Box-folder 5:79)
  - Hubbard, J. M., 1897; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box5:80 (Box-folder 5:80)
  - Hubbard, J. M., 1895; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box5:81 (Box 5, Folder 81)
  - Hubbard, J. M., 1896; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box5:82 (Box 5, Folder 82)
  - Hubbard, J. M., 1888-1894; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box5:83 (Box 5, Folder 83)
  - Hulett, N. P., 1903; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box5:84 (Box 5, Folder 84)
  - Hurlbut, Charles S., 1904-1905; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box5:85 (Box-folder 5:85)
  - Hyde, Andrew, 1898; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box5:86 (Box 5, Folder 86)
  - Hungary, 1913; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box5:87 (Box 5, Folder 87, Box-folder 5:87)
    Agricultural experiment stations; Correspondence; Hungary (nation); Storrs Agricultural Experiment Station
  - I - J, 1900-1901; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box5:88 (Box 5, Folder 88)
    Correspondence; Storrs Agricultural Experiment Station
  - I - K, 1898; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box5:89 (Box 5, Folder 89)
  - K - L, 1898; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box5:90 (Box 5, Folder 90)
  - I - J, 1902; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box5:91 (Box 5, Folder 91)
  - I - M, 1903; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box5:92 (Box 5, Folder 92)
  - H - I, 1903; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box5:93 (Box-folder 5:93)
  - Ignatiev-Illinois Seed, 1907-1917; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:94 (Box-folder 6:94, Box 6, Folder 94)
  - Illinois, University of, Agricultural Experiment Station, 1904-1920; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:95 (Box 6, Folder 95, Box-folder 6:95)
  - Improved Mailing-Inderelst, 1908-1919; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:96 (Box-folder 6:96, Box 6, Folder 96)
  - India, 1898-1916; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:97 (Box-folder 6:97, Box 6, Folder 97)
  - Indianapolis Engraving and Electrotyping Company, 1908; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:98 (Box 6, Folder 98, Box-folder 6:98)
  - Ingerson, F. N., 1910; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:99 (Box-folder 6:99, Box 6, Folder 99)
  - Ingomar Poultry Supply Company, 1913-1914; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:100 (Box-folder 6:100, Box 6, Folder 100)
  - Ingraham-International Cheese, 1906-1916; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:101 (Box-folder 6:101, Box 6, Folder 101)
  - Institute Programs, 1907; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:102 (Box 6, Folder 102, Box-folder 6:102)
  - International Harvester Company of America, 1907-1920; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:103 (Box 6, Folder 103, Box-folder 6:103)
  - International Stock Food Company, 1907; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:104 (Box 6, Folder 104, Box-folder 6:104)
  - Interstate Chemical-Iorns, 1907-1917; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:105 (Box-folder 6:105, Box 6, Folder 105)
  - Iowa State College Agricultural Experiment Station, 1907-1920; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:106 (Box-folder 6:106, Box 6, Folder 106)
  - Irwin, L. P., 1910; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:107 (Box-folder 6:107, Box 6, Folder 107)
  - Issajeff, Theodore, 1905-1907; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:108 (Box 6, Folder 108, Box-folder 6:108)
  - Isbill-Ison, 1908-1918; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:109 (Box-folder 6:109, Box 6, Folder 109)
  - Italy, 1898-1914; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:110 (Box 6, Folder 110, Box-folder 6:110)
  - Ithaca Calendar Clock Company, 1906; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:111 (Box-folder 6:111, Box 6, Folder 111)
  - Ithaca Trust Company, 1905; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:112 (Box 6, Folder 112, Box-folder 6:112)
  - Ives, C.P., 1910; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:113 (Box-folder 6:113, Box 6, Folder 113)
  - Ives, E. M., 1904-1908; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:114 (Box-folder 6:114, Box 6, Folder 114)
  - Ives, Joel S., 1910-1911; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:115 (Box-folder 6:115, Box 6, Folder 115)
  - Ives, Julius, 1907-1908; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:116 (Box 6, Folder 116, Box-folder 6:116)
  - Ives, Paul P., 1910-1911; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:117 (Box-folder 6:117, Box 6, Folder 117)
  - Jacksonville-Jackson, H. H., 1910-1918; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:118 (Box-folder 6:118, Box 6, Folder 118)
  - Jackson, John H., 1902-1910; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:119 (Box-folder 6:119, Box 6, Folder 119)
  - Jackson Mushroom Farm, 1910; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:120 (Box 6:120, Box 6, Folder 120)
  - Jackson, William-Jacobs, 1908-1919; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:121 (Box 6, Folder 121, Box-folder 6:121)
  - Jagger, Mary, 1913; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:122 (Box-folder 6:122, Box 6, Folder 122)
  - James-Janssen, 1911-1920; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:123 (Box 6, Folder 123, Box-folder 6:123)
  - Japan, 1899-1913; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:124 (Box-folder 6:124, Box 6, Folder 124)
  - Jardin-Jarmolow, 1908-1918; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:125 (Box-folder 6:125, Box 6, Folder 125)
  - Jarvis, C. D., 1906-1917; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:126 (Box-folder 6:126, Box 6, Folder 126)
  - Jarvis, Charles M., 1904-1917; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:127 (Box 6, Folder 127, Box-folder 6:127)
  - Jarvis, Lucy, 1910; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:128 (Box-folder 6:128, Box 6, Folder 128)
  - J. B. Ford Company, 1908; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:129 (Box 6, Folder 129, Box-folder 6:129)
  - Jeffers, Henry W., 1907-1911; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:130 (Box-folder 6:130, Box 6, Folder 130)
  - Jeffrey-Jenkins, Charles, 1910-1917; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:131 (Box 6, Folder 131, Box-folder 6:131)
  - Jenkins, E. H., 1888-1903; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:132 (Box-folder 6:132, Box 6, Folder 132)
  - Jenkins, E. H., 1904-1919; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:133 (Box-folder 6:133, Box 6, Folder 133)
  - Jenks-Jewell Belting, 1903-1920; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:134 (Box 6, Folder 134, Box-folder 6:134)
  - Jewell, Harvey, 1903-1911; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:135 (Box 6, Folder 135, Box-folder 6:135)
  - Jewett, A. C.-Jewett, R. A., 1917-1920; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:136 (Box 6, Folder 136, Box-folder 6:136)
  - J.H. Hale, 1906; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:137 (Box 6, Folder 137, Box-folder 6:137)
  - Jilson, L. W., 1909-1911; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:138 (Box 6, Folder 138, Box-folder 6:138)
  - J. H. McFarland Company, 1914; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:139 (Box 6, Folder 139, Box-folder 6:139)
  - Job, Herbert K., 1910-1913; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:140 (Box 6, Folder 140, Box-folder 6:140)
  - Jodman-Johansen, J., 1907-1917; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:141 (Box-folder 6:141, Box 6, Folder 141)
  - Johansen, S., 1918; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:142 (Box 6, Folder 142, Box-folder 6:142)
  - John Deere Plow Company, 1910-1914; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:143 (Box 6, Folder 143, Box-folder 6:143)
  - John F. Convey Cigar Company, 1908-1909; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:144 (Box 6, Folder 144, Box-folder 6:144)
  - Johns-Johnson, Riley, 1903-1920; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:145 (Box 6, Folder 145, Box-folder 6:145)
  - Johnson, S. W., 1892-1896; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:146 (Box 6, Folder 146, Box-folder 6:146)
  - Johnson, Samuel E., 1903; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:147 (Box 6, Folder 147, Box-folder 6:147)
  - Johnson, Wallace R., 1917; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:148 (Box 6, Folder 148, Box-folder 6:148)
  - Johnson, William-Jones, D. E., 1903-1920; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:149 (Box-folder 6:149, Box 6, Folder 149)
  - Jones, D. F., 1917-1919; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:150 (Box-folder 6:150, Box 6, Folder 150)
  - Jones, E. A., 1906-1917; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:151 (Box-folder 6:151, Box 6, Folder 151)
  - Jones, Earl-Jordan, Frank, 1908-1920; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:152 (Box-folder 6:152, Box 6, Folder 152)
  - Jordan Hardware Company, 1907-1918; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:153 (Box 6, Folder 153, Box-folder 6:153)
  - Jordan, James-Juckett, 1907-1918; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:154 (Box-folder 6:154, Box 6, Folder 154)
  - Judd, C. M., 1911-1913; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:155 (Box-folder 6:155, Box 6, Folder 155)
  - Judd, H.C. And Root Wool, 1907-1910; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:156 (Box-folder 6:156, Box 6, Folder 156)
  - Judd, James S., 1896-1897; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:157 (Box-folder 6:157, Box 6, Folder 157)
  - Judd, P. H.-Judd, William, 1908-1916; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:158 (Box-folder 6:158, Box 6, Folder 158)
  - Judkins-Jussel, 1904-1915; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:159 (Box-folder 6:159, Box 6, Folder 159)
  - J.W. Biles Company, 1907; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:160 (Box-folder 6:160, Box 6, Folder 160)
  - Kains-Kampe, 1907-1920; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:161 (Box 6, Folder 161, Box-folder 6:161)
  - Kansas, 1907-1920; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:162 (Box-folder 6:162, Box 6, Folder 162)
  - Kansas State Agricultural College, 1905-1920; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:163 (Box-folder 6:163, Box 6, Folder 163)
  - Kaplan-Karnopp, 1907-1917; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:164 (Box-folder 6:164, Box 6, Folder 164)
  - Kasovich, I., 1907-1908; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:165 (Box-folder 6:165, Box 6, Folder 165)
  - Kathan-Keeney, C. A., 1903-1920; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:166 (Box 6, Folder 166, Box-folder 6:166)
  - Keeney, Caroline S., 1910-1919; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:167 (Box-folder 6:167, Box 6, Folder 167)
  - Keeney, Charles-Kellogg, H., 1904-1920; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:168 (Box 6, Folder 168, Box-folder 6:168)
  - Kellogg, L. F., 1910-1916; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:169 (Box 6, Folder 169, Box-folder 6:169)
  - Kellogg's Teacher's Agency, 1919-1920; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:170 (Box 6, Folder 170, Box-folder 6:170)
  - Kellogg Toasted-Kenny, H. A., 1904-1920; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:171 (Box-folder 6:171, Box 6, Folder 171)
  - Kentucky, State University of, 1908-1920; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:172 (Box 6, Folder 172, Box-folder 6:172)
  - Kentucky Tobacco-Kernen, 1903-1917; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:173 (Box-folder 6:173, Box 6, Folder 173)
  - Kerr, R. H., 1905; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:174 (Box 6, Folder 174, Box-folder 6:174)
  - Ketchin-Kilbride, Ellen, 1903-1920; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:175 (Box-folder 6:175, Box 6, Folder 175)
  - Kilbride, J. B., 1917-1919; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:176 (Box 6, Folder 176, Box-folder 6:176)
  - Kimball's-King, William, 1902-1920; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:177 (Box 6, Folder 177, Box-folder 6:177)
  - Kingsbury, Andrew, 1903-1906; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:178 (Box 6, Folder 178, Box-folder 6:178)
  - Kingsbury, C. S.-Kirkpatrick, Amanda, 1902-1917; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:179 (Box 6, Folder 179, Box-folder 6:179)
  - Kirkpatrick, William F., 1912-1920; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:180 (Box 6, Folder 180, Box-folder 6:180)
  - Kirtland-Kloss, 1907-1919; 1972-0001\SeriesI:Correspondence\Box6:181 (Box 6, Folder 181, Box-folder 6:181)